(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-07T05:34:16.621306",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
With Announcement! Birds NIGHT OUT - Pavolia Reine Birthday 2024 -
[Announcement: Birds NIGHT OUT - Pavolia Reine Birthday 2024]
START 2024.09.09 20:00 WIB / 22:00 JST
Birds NIGHT OUT - Pavolia Reine Birthday 2024
I drink good coffee every morning
It comes from a place that's far away
And when I'm done, I feel like talking
Without you here, there's less to say
I don't want you thinking I'm unhappy
What is closer to the truth
Is if I lived til I was a hundred and two
I just don't think I'll ever get over you
Na-Na-Na-Na-Na, Ready for my show
Okay, たちまち 独壇場
Okay, a one-person show right away
Listen, listen
Na-Na-Na-Na-Na, Ready for my show
傾け
Tilt your head
振り切ろう
Let's shake it off
ヤーヤーヤーヤーヤーヤー 唱タイム
Yah-yah-yah-yah-yah-yah, Show time
天辺の御成り ほら おいで
Behold the summit's arrival, come on over
宵をコンプリート オーライ
Complete the night, alright
だんだんノリノリで超 簡単 Brah, Brah, Brah! Pow
Getting into it step by step, super easy, Brah, Brah, Brah! Pow
ええい言われない Ain’t nobody stop
No matter what they say, ain't nobody stop
全土絢爛豪華
Splendid and gorgeous across the land
Attention 騒ごうか
Attention, shall we make some noise?
意思表示にもうじき衝撃の声高らか 堂々登板
Soon expressing intent with a resounding impact, taking the stage proudly
もう藍洞は遠くの轟々脱皮 壊れよう誰も知らぬ
The blue cave sheds far away in a roar, breaking unnoticed
疾っくの疾うの淘法 栄光を跨ごう 御出座しだ Ah
Long past panning methods, let's span across glory, making our grand entrance Ah
格好つけてるつもりは No, No
Thinking I'm just trying to look cool? No, no
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
Nah-nah, nah-nah-nah, ready for my show
あ、たちまち独占舞台 Listen listen
Ah, instantly monopolizing the stage, listen, listen
Okay、即刻独占舞台 Listen listen
Okay, immediately monopolizing the stage, listen, listen
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
Nah-nah, nah-nah-nah, ready for my show
傾け振れ切ろう
Tilt it and push it to the limit
Ya-ya-ya-ya-ya Show Time
Ya-ya-ya-ya-ya, showtime!
頂上見て見なここへ
Look at the peak right here
酔い潰れていいから
It's fine if you drink 'til you pass out
All right テンション上がって
All right, tension rising high,
ぶらりぶらりくだらない日々よ
oh, these wandering, pointless days—
さようなら 脳汁垂れ流すように
farewell! Like letting your brain juice overflow,
お前に夢中なジュース
a juice you're obsessed with—
味わい尽くす前に
before savoring it all,
かっとなっちゃえば？
why not snap and lose your cool?
Why not snap and lose your cool?
かっとなっちゃえば？
カルマに至る前に掠うわ
Snatch it all before reaching karma!
低音響かせろ
Let the bass resonate!
なんだかなって つまらないこともあるでしょう
There must be times when things feel dull and pointless,
ロンリー論理のノート ハンディー本気脱走
a lonely logic notebook, handy serious escape—
やんなっちゃって泥に Bad
getting sick of it and falling deep in bad mud!
ご法度だろうが 浸れて堕ちて
Even if it's forbidden, soak in it and fall,
もっと頑張って アガるまでもっと頑張って
try harder, work harder until you soar!
繋がろうひとりよりふたり
Let's connect, two is better than one,
増えたら安心 心配ないや
once it grows we're safe, no worries at all!
Alright 任せて don't mind
Alright, leave it to me, don't mind!
波あり難題 みんなで乗っかっちゃえば案外さくっと行いそう
Troubles with waves, if everyone jumps in, we might pull it off easily!
半端なら K.O.
Half-heartedness means K.O.!
開演準備しちゃおうか
Shall we get ready for the show?
泣いてても笑ってても
Whether you're crying or smiling,
愛してね
love me, okay?
ほら Say No
Come on, say no!
低音響かせろ
Let the bass resonate!
今宵は暗転パーティ
Tonight is a blackout party!
踊り明かせ 踊り明かせ
Dance the night away, dance away,
孤独は殺菌
loneliness is sterilized,
満員御礼
a full house, thank you!
痛みまで おシェアで
Share even the pain together,
ここらでバイバイ let go
say goodbye around here and let go!
どんな劣等感だてて 即興の血小板で
No matter what inferiority complex, with improvised platelets,
抑え込んで 突っ込んで 仕舞い込んじゃうでしょ
holding it down, thrusting in, you tuck it all away, right?
Up and down なテンション ねぇまいっちゃうっていの相当
Up-and-down tension, hey, it's driving me pretty crazy!
ドバッと噴き出すのは 本音の独り言
Gushing out in a flood is my honest soliloquy—
「別に興味ない」
"I'm not really interested,"
「特に関係ない」
"it has nothing to do with me."
塞ぎ込んで 舌先絶頂へ
Shutting myself in, heading to the tip of my tongue's ecstasy!
合図を奏でて PrrPrrPrr
Play the signal, prr-prr-prr!
ほら集まって夜行だ 鳴っていこうぜ
Come on, gather up, it's a night parade, let's make some noise!
半端なら K.O.
Half-heartedness means K.O.!
踊り明かせ 踊り明かせ 孤独は殺菌
Dance away, dance away, loneliness is sterilized,
満員御礼
a full house, thank you!
痛みまで おシェアで
Share even the pain together,
今宵も暗転パーティだ
tonight is a blackout party too!
またのお越しを
We'll surely meet again,
きっと
surely...
次回までお元気に
until next time, stay well!
ここらでバイバイ let go
Say goodbye around here and let go!
描いたDaybreak
Painted daybreak...
肺活低音狂
Lung-capacity low-frequency madness!
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
Nah-nah, nah-nah-nah, ready for my show!
例の危険度 比類なき活気充満
That customary level of danger, peerlessly full of vitality!
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
Nah-nah, nah-nah-nah, ready for my show!
石川 鉢川 鳴呼
Ishikawa, hachikawa, ahh—!
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
Nah-nah, nah-nah-nah, ready for my show!
存分に騒ぎ切る事 叫べよ叫べよ
Make the most of partying it up, shout it out, shout it out!
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
Nah-nah, nah-nah-nah, ready for my show!
巻き起こすために Stay Stay Stay
To stir it up, stay, stay, stay!
一切合切忘れて叫べよ
Forget everything completely and shout it out!
Aye, Wah oh oh oh
Aye, wah-oh-oh-oh!
右に左まとめて Pull up
Gather to the right and left, pull up!
思い切り一気に かっとなっちゃえば？
With all your might, why not snap in one go?
なにはともあれが勝負の流儀 Shout it out, shout it out
Whatever the case, winning is the way—shout it out, shout it out!
チート、gifted、荒技、wanted
Cheat, gifted, rough skills, wanted!
禁忌、禁じ手、明らかな盲点
Taboo, forbidden move, obvious blind spot!
反則、異次元、この世の中のもんではないです
Foul play, otherworldly, not of this world at all!
無理ゲー、それ聞いてないって...
Impossible game, nobody told me about that...
ay ライバル口を揃えて wow ライバル口を揃えて
Ay, rivals in unison—wow, rivals in unison!
バグって、まぐれ、認めねーゼッテー
Bugging out, fluke, I'll never admit it!
マジで？コレおま…全部生身で？
Seriously? Hey you... all in the flesh?
It's生身 It's生身 yeah yeah yeah yeah
It's flesh, it's flesh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
実力を発揮し切る前に
Before fully unleashing my true ability,
相手の方がバックれててらしい
looks like the opponent backed out and fled!
上がり切るハードル very happy
Hurdles raised to the max, very happy!
相変わらず脱皮してる毎日
Still shedding my skin day after day,
誰の七光も要らないお前のiceより icy
needing no borrowed light, icier than your ice!
俺、パッと見出来ないことばかりだけど very happy あ、キテる…呆れてる周り
I can barely do anything at first glance, but very happy—ah, they're fed up... people around are appalled!
恵まれてる家族友達
Blessed with family and friends,
もう反則的立ち位置、皆俺に任せとけば良い
already in a foul-play position, just leave it all to me!
教科書に無い 問題集に無い 超BADな呪い listen
Not in textbooks, not in workbooks, a super BAD curse, listen!
鏡よ鏡答えちゃって Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
Mirror, mirror on the wall, give me the answer, who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah!
生身のまま行けるところまで
Staying in the flesh as far as I can go,
To the next, To the 1番上
to the next, to the very top!
Now singin’ Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
Now singin' bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born...
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超flex
Eyday, just staying as I am is super flex!
Eyday 誰も口を挟めない
Eyday, nobody can interrupt!
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超flex Eyday 誰も口を挟ませない
Eyday, just staying as I am is super flex, eyday, nobody can let anyone interrupt!
学歴も無い 前科も無い 余裕で
No educational background, no criminal record, with ease—
この存在自体が文化財な脳味噌
this very existence is a cultural asset of a brain!
高級車は買える 免許は無い 愛車
Can buy a luxury car, but no driver's license—my beloved car!
全国各地揺らす逸品 このベロが
An exquisite gem shaking nationwide, this tongue of mine—
バレットなら満タン 関西訛り 生身のコトダマ
fully loaded with bullets, Kansai accent, living words of power!
音楽、幸運、勝利の女神 今宵も三股 bang, bang
Goddess of music, luck, and victory, three-timing tonight too, bang, bang!
漫画みたいな絵柄とまんまに張り合えしまってる漫画
Competing head-on with an anime-like style, a manga come to life!
圧倒的チカラ この頭と口から この身体
Overwhelming power from this head and mouth, this body—
tattooは入って無い このツラに傷もついて無い
no tattoos entered, no scars on this face either!
繰り返しやらかしてダメージがイカつい年輪を刻む皺
Repeating screw-ups, the damage carves tough annual rings and wrinkles!
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
鏡よ鏡答えちゃって Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
Mirror, mirror on the wall, give me the answer, who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah!
生身のまま行けるところまで
Staying in the flesh as far as I can go,
To the next, To the 1番上
to the next, to the very top!
Now singin’ Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
Now singin' bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born...
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超flex Eyday 誰も口を挟めない
Eyday, just staying as I am is super flex, eyday, nobody can interrupt!
チート、gifted、荒技、wanted 禁忌、禁じ手
Cheating, gifted, rough techniques, wanted...
明らかなり盲点 反則、異次元、この世の中のもんでは無いです
Contraindications, prohibitions, clearly a blind spot...
Kiss me, keep those lips from wandering off
Tell me every sweet and tender thought
Give me all you have to give and more
Fantasy's where futures are born!
Can you feel the beat? The rhythm, the tune
Your heart and mine, the countdown
If you feel something coming to you
Believe it and scream it aloud!
I don't think I'll miss you anymore, like I did the day you left
There's so many just like you, I could use instead
'Cause passion burning bright only hurts you in the end
This city will swallow the pain
Tomorrow's another today
Curtain call's at dawn, darling, showtime
Spend our moment dancing in the moonlight
'Til your gaze starts swaying with my body, keep your eyes on me
Take me somewhere, deep into the night
Touch me, here, there, anywhere you like
Trust me, won't you let me look inside?
Fantasies and futures collide
It's just the two of us beneath the starry sky...
If the only way to keep on living is keep on living strong
Then you can keep the kindness, 'cause I'm moving on
No need to say goodbye to me, I'm already gone
Just wipe all your tears away
And know we'll start over someday...
All your heart, your soul, your body, you belong to one and only
Unconditionally yearning, knowing no one else will do...
Can you feel the bond between us grow tight? We're closer than we've ever been!
Follow me, match your rhythm to mine, and let it all out from within!
I don't think I'll miss you anymore, like I did the day you left
I won't say I love you, I know I'll take it back
I'm used to this, I'm not the same old loser that burned bright and quick, when candles and wind could never last
A city that's living in fast-forward's
the perfect place for lovers like us to take a chance
There's nothing here to stop us when in Rome, romance, and I won't let you leave me alone without a dance!
I don't wanna hear a goodbye...
Don't break the illusion tonight...
Curtain call's at dawn, darling, showtime
Spend forever living 'til the sunrise!
Feel that look, even with the lights off
Dance until we drop!
Wow, hello everybody!
This is my, my very, very first 3D live concert!
What do you think about it so far?
And this is the hashtag ReineMeptember2024.
So Reine and pe-pe-pe-pe, you know, the sound I make, September, and this year 2024, easy to remember, right?
So, I'm looking forward to your posts and your consoles, you know, what you think about it on X, okay? Please do post a lot, I will be looking.
And so, so the idea behind this live event today is rave.
And so, the idea behind this live event today is rave.
I want you to see a cool side of me...
Biasanya kan super elegant business... super elegant. Elegant, elegant banget.
Usually it's super elegant business... super elegant. Elegant, very elegant.
Gitu, aku kan biasanya elegant, gitu.
You know, I'm usually elegant, like that.
Tapi jadi sekarang tuh pengennya tuh yang, oh, aku mau ngasih lihat yang keren, gitu.
But now I want something like, "Oh, I want to show something cool," you know.
Ya pokoknya gitu deh, ya inilah.
Yeah, anyway, like that, yeah, this is it.
Terus kayak di atas tuh ada mirrorball, keren banget.
And then up there, there's a mirror ball, it's so cool.
Jadi itu pokoknya rave banget. It's so rave boy! And there's so many planets, keren kan? Keren kan? Keren enggak sih? Keren enggak sih?
So it's totally rave-ish. It's so rave boy! And there's so many planets, isn't it cool? Isn't it cool? Isn't it cool? Isn't it cool?
And then there's lasers as well. You guys saw, right?
Yeah, bola disko mantap.
Yeah, disco ball is awesome.
Terus ada juga, there's also audio spectrum everywhere. You guys saw it, right? Anyone here noticed?
And then there's also, there's also audio spectrum everywhere. You guys saw it, right? Anyone here noticed?
During the performance? Well, they're not here right now though. The audio spectrums, they move in sync with the music. Ooh!
For those who didn't notice, I hope you pay attention to them in the upcoming songs, okay? Yeah, it's super cool.
Eh, ya gitu deh. Pokoknya keren banget. Ada warnanya biru. Jadi ini biasanya tuh biru, kayak gini sekarang biru tapi bisa warna-warni sesuai lagu.
Uh, yeah, like that. Anyway, it's really cool. There's a blue color. So usually it's blue, like this now it's blue but it can be colorful depending on the song.
Aku juga udah siapkan setlist dengan lagu-lagu yang asyik banget buat joget.
I've also prepared a setlist with songs that are super fun to dance to.
Buhar cocok sama vibe rave-nya, ne?
Perfectly matching the rave vibe, right?
Pokoknya the songs are very very rave boy deh. And then apa ya?
Anyway, the songs are very, very rave boy. And then what else?
And then, the songs I sang, it was Show, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born, I had the hat on. Nggak tahu, I don't have it anymore, but, ya, I had them on.
And then the songs I sang, it was Show, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born, I had the hat on. Now I don't have it anymore, but yeah, I had them on.
And then, if you missed it, well, sorry, they were bangers so please do check out the archive.
And also for Illusion Night, well, it's Illusion Night. Well, no, you know Illusion Night, for those of you who don't know, I'm streaming Illusion Night, okay?
And also for Illusion Night, well, it's Illusion Night. Well, you know Illusion Night, for those of you who don't know, I'm streaming Illusion Night, okay?
And up next, we have many many guests making appearances, so please, please, please look forward to it, okay? Habis ini bakal ada banyak tamu yang tampil, jadi nanti stay, oke?
And up next, we have many many guests making appearances, so please, please, please look forward to it, okay? After this, there will be many guests performing, so stay tuned, okay?
But, before we go to the next song, I will take a moment to get ready, okay? Ganti baju dulu guys.
But, before we go to the next song, I will take a moment to get ready, okay? Let's change clothes first, guys.
Aku mau ganti baju, ganti baju, ganti baju.
I'm going to change clothes, change clothes, change clothes.
DADDY! DADDY! DO! 欲しいのさ
DADDY! DADDY! DO! I want it so badly,
あなたのすべてが 愛に抱かれ
for everything about you to be embraced by love,
キラキラ燃えてしまいたい
shining and burning away!
可憐な KISSで
With a lovely kiss,
目線そらして ズルいよね
you avert your gaze, how cunning of you!
火照り出す ボクの気持ち
My feelings begin to flush,
もてあそぶみたいに
as if to toy with me.
追いかけちゃ ダメなのは
Chasing after you is forbidden,
わかってる でも無理さ 一度踏み出せば
I know that, but it's impossible once I take that step!
戻れなくて
There's no turning back!
仮面は脱ぎ捨てていけない
You can't just take off your mask,
言葉より 遊びが本気になる
actions speak louder than play, turning real!
DADDY! DADDY! DO! 欲しいのさ
DADDY! DADDY! DO! I want it so badly,
あなたのすべてが
for everything about you
騙されたら それでもいい
to be tricked—even if so, it's fine!
もっと震わせて 魅せてくれ
Make me tremble more, show it to me,
僕だけに 笑顔の裏まで
only to me, even behind your smile!
愛に抱かれ キラキラ燃えてしまいたい
Held in love, I want to burn and sparkle brightly!
駆け引きなど しないの
Playing games is something I won't do,
二度と会えない 人だから
since you're someone I'll never meet again.
後悔に暮れるなら 恋の火に焼かれたい
If I'm to drown in regret, I'd rather burn in the fire of love!
わざとでしょう 流し目が 愛しさを 刺激する
It's on purpose, isn't it? Your sidelong glance stimulates my affection,
そっと振り返る 美しさに
and as you gently turn back, in your beauty,
心はつかまれて 呼吸が
my heart is captured, and my breath
止まって
stops!
遊びが本気になる
Play turns into something real!
DADDY! DADDY! DO! ぶつけたい
DADDY! DADDY! DO! I want to hurl
想いのすべてを
all of my feelings!
綺麗なものだけじゃなくて
Not just beautiful things,
危険な願いも 止めないで
don't stop my dangerous wishes either!
その声が 僕を連れていく
That voice of yours leads me away.
愛に抱かれ キラキラ燃えてしまいたい
Held in love, I want to burn and sparkle brightly!
燃えてしまいたい
I want to burn up
あなただけとゆうくちびるが
The lips that say "only you"
優しく微笑むたび
Every time they smile so gently
飲み込まれて
Swallowed up
いざなわれて
Led astray
未知の世界触れて
Touching an unknown world
OH
最後まで あなたにゆだねて
Entrusting myself to you until the very end
壊れるなら それでもいい
If I break, even that is fine
もっと狂わせて
Drive me even more mad
見せてくれ 僕だけに
Show me, only to me
こころの奥まで 愛に抱かれ
Embraced by love to the depths of my heart
ギラ
Dazzling
燃えたい いのち果てぬ夜明けまで
I want to burn, until the dawn of my fading life
パッパラ
Pappara
寂しくて眠れぬ日も
Even on lonely, sleepless nights
今夜たりさよならできる気がする胸の高鳴り
tonight I feel like I can say goodbye, my heart is thumping
見すかされた行方知れずの気持ち隠しても既に遠いわ
Even if I hide these feelings of unknown whereabouts, they are already far away
世の常 今から全てで飛ばしてあげる
It's the way of the world; I'll send it all flying from now on
センセーション 愛想ぶらずに
Sensation, without putting on a fake smile
センセーション 巻き起こすのよ
Sensation, stirring it up
センセーション どこ吹く風も理解を通り越して
Sensation, letting the wind blow past all comprehension
センセーション なんて素敵な
Sensation, how wonderful
絶頂感 満ち溢れてく
Overflowing with a climactic feeling
私が何者もどうでもいいからほらその手で深くへ
Whoever I am doesn't matter, so come on, deeper with those hands
混ざり合わなくても愛しているのは
Even if we don't blend, what I love is...
センセーション 愛想ぶらずに
Sensation, without putting on a fake smile
センセーション 巻き起こすのよ
Sensation, stirring it up
センセーション どこ吹く風も理解を通り越して
Sensation, letting the wind blow past all comprehension
センセーション なんて素敵な
Sensation, how wonderful
絶頂感 満ち溢れてく
Overflowing with a climactic feeling
私が何者もどうでもいいからほらその手で深くへ
Whoever I am doesn't matter, so come on, deeper with those hands
合わせることもなく
Without even matching up
Wow! That was two more songs!
二曲目でした。いかがだったでしょうか？
That was two songs. How was it?
The first song I sang, Daddidatididoo, together with a very very special guest called Reine Bogel.
The first song I sang was "DADDY ! DADDY ! DO !" with a very, very special guest called Reine Bogel.
可愛かったでしょう？
Wasn't she cute? Reine Bogel...
I would want one Reine Bogel in my home, you would want one too, right?
pokoknya for this song, I've always wanted to sing this song in like an official live and I finally can do it, so I'm very happy happy happy about it.
Anyway, for this song, I've always wanted to sing it in an official live and I finally could do it, so I'm very, very happy about it.
And for the second song, I sang... apa ya? Wait, it's Passionet 3. Sensation. Yes, I did it!
And for the second song, I sang... what was it? Wait, it's "PaⅢ.SENSATION". Yes, I did it!
I personally invited other holomen...
I personally invited other holomem...
senpai and not senpais, we have
Lamy, we have Kanata
senpai, we have what was it,
Wawa, Kiara and me
together! And...
Kanauru, Kobo and MC
Gamo, gumu, gumu, Samagum, Kitakan tewana!
Gomawayan ingni-roro...
Yo! Who taught you that?
Kiki, kiki, I taught it myself because I'm from Hololive Indonesia!
Maya! E-maya! Really?
And I have no memo in my hands, no, no, it's secret, secret...
Secret, secret memo, mm yeah, very Holo Indonesia guys, for me, Holo Indonesia.
So, um, okay, well...
I don't know if it's okay for her to be here. Is it okay? Yes, sure!
Dandak dandak dandak... Donjok donjok, yoru de, yoru de, okay okay.
Well, okay, well, since she's here anyway, what do you think about the song?
Oh, I always love your song choices. I think you're a genius in putting the right people together with the right song.
Aw, thank you! And I also really love your Beat Eater cover that you did long time ago. I always listen to it, it's my favorite!
Yeah, and now you get to do a mature cool, so I've always wanted to do it, you know, like with like a ooh for people, you know, spicy, right?
Very spicy! Always spicy!
Always always spicy, spicy, spicy! Did you guys miss PavoNashi?
Ooh, PavoNashi?
Yeah, we've been together so many times now.
I know, I was in your live last time, right? My birthday, and that was first in your 3D debut.
Oh oh, we also sang a spicy song then! Yeah!
So it's kind of like the spicy tradition, let's go, keep it going!
We like it spicy, well I like it sweet, but sweet and spicy, it's a good combo, right? Yay!
Okay, what should we say? What should we say? I want to do
our bird mating dance!
Oh! Okay, okay, okay, we can do that! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
It's from a long time ago.
Do you guys know the OG PavoNashi lore?
Do you remember it? Do you remember it?
Do it with us! Yes! Do it with us! Bird mating dance!
Yeah, okay, so I okay, okay, okay.
Three, two, one, and!
Are you doing that properly?
Well, you can't! Let's do it once more! Okay!
Happy Birthday!
Thank you for your birthday! I was going to make it better if she was going to forget or not!
Okay, bye-bye!
Makasih! Thank you banget Kiara udah datang, guys. Thank you so much even though she's not supposed to be here. Thank you so much Kiara for coming.
Makasih! Thank you so much Kiara for coming, guys. Thank you so much even though she's not supposed to be here. Thank you so much Kiara for coming.
And next up we still have more songs and more guests, that's right! You heard it right. So please stay tuned for the next song!
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
With an invincible smile, disrupting the media
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
Wanting to know that secret, mysterious
抜けてるとこさえ彼女のエリア
Even her clumsy side is part of her territory
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You, who are perfect and a liar,
天才的なアイドル様
Are a genius idol-sama!
今日何食べた?
What did you eat today?
好きな本は?
What book do you like?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの?
If you go out to play, where do you go?
何も食べてない それは内緒
Haven't eaten anything, that's a secret
何を聞かれてものらりくらり
No matter what you're asked, evasive and nonchalant
そう淡々とだけど燦々と
So calmly, yet brilliantly shining
見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
Secrets almost seen are like the taste of honey
あれもないないない これもないないない
There's none of that, none of this either
好きなタイプは? 相手は? さあ答えて
What's your type? Who's your partner? Now answer!
「誰かを好きになることなんて私分からないくてさ」
"I don't even know what it's like to love someone"
嘘か本当か知り得ない
Unknowable if it's a lie or truth
そんな言葉にまた一人堕ちる
Falling for those words once again, another person falls
また好きにさせる
Making them fall in love once more
誰かの目を奪っていく
Stealing everyone's gaze
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
You are the perfect and ultimate idol!
金輪際現れない
Never to appear again
一番星の生まれ変わりだ
Reincarnation of the morning star
ああ、その笑顔で愛してるで
Ah, with that smile, saying "I love you"
誰も彼も虜にしていく
Captivating everyone, one by one
その瞳が その言葉が 嘘でもそれは完全なアイ
Even if those eyes, those words are lies, that is absolute love!
はいはいあの子は特別です
Yes, yes, that girl is special
我々はハナからおまけです
We're just extras from the start
お星様の引き立て役です
We're just background props for the star
全てがあの子のお陰なわけない
No way everything is thanks to her!
洒落臭い 妬み嫉妬なんてない
Impudent, no jealousy or envy at all—no way!
わけがない これをネタじゃない
This isn't a joke, that's why I can't forgive it!
完璧じゃない 君じゃ許せない
Imperfect you, I can't forgive you!
自分を許せない 誰よりも強い 君以外は認めない
Can't forgive myself, I accept no one stronger than you!
誰もが信じ崇めてる
Everyone believes and worships
まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
Truly the strongest and invincible idol!
弱点なんて見当たらない
Not a single weakness to be found
一番星を宿している
Housing the morning star
弱いとこなんて見せちゃダメダメ
Mustn't show any weak spots, no no!
知りたいことは見せずに 唯一無二じゃなくちゃイヤイヤ
Without showing what they want to know, must be one and only, no no!
それこそ本物のアイ
That right there is true love!
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
Stirring up the media with invincible smiles,
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
that mysterious secret everyone wants to know.
抜け出しているとこさえ彼女のエリア
Even her unguarded moments are part of her special domain.
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You are a perfect and deceitful
天才的なアイドル様
genius idol-sama!
今日何食べた？ 好きな本は？
What did you eat today? What's your favorite book?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
When you go out to play, where do you go?
何も食べてない それは内緒
"I haven't eaten anything. That's a secret."
何を聞かれてものらりくらり
No matter what you're asked, you deftly dodge it,
そう淡々と だけど燦々と
so coolly, yet shining brilliantly.
見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
That hard-to-reach secret is sweet like honey.
あれもないないない これもないないない
There's nothing like this, nothing like that.
好きなタイプは？ 相手は？ さあ答えて
What's your type? Who's the partner? Come on, answer!
「誰かを好きになることなんて私分からないからさ」
"I wouldn't even know how to fall in love with someone."
嘘か本当か知り得ないそんな言葉に
Caught once again in those words of unknown truth,
また一万人を虜にする
captivating countless people once more.
誰かが目を奪われていく
Everyone's eyes are stolen away,
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
you are the perfect and ultimate idol.
金輪際現れない
One who will never appear again,
一番星の生まれ変わり
the reincarnation of the brightest star.
その笑顔で愛してるで誰もかも虜にしていく
Captivating everyone with that smiling "I love you,"
その瞳が その言葉が
those eyes, those words—
嘘でもそれは完璧なアイ
even if a lie, it's the ultimate AI.
はいはいあの子は特別です
Yes, yes, that girl is special.
私たちはハラタリサブ
We are merely supporting background.
ないないありえない私を可愛いなんて
No, no, way out of line to call me cute.
言ったその丸が歌い踊る私はマリア
The circle that said it sings and dances, I am Maria.
そう嘘にとびきりの愛だ
Yes, a lie is the greatest love of all.
愛してる
I love you.
どうでもいいような夜だけど
It's an ordinary, don't-care kind of night, but
響めき 煌めきと君も
the hustle, the sparkle, and you as well.
まだ止まった 刻む針も
The stopped, ticking clock hands
入り浸った 散らかる部屋も
and the cluttered, lingering room
変わらないね 思い出しては二人
haven't changed. Whenever I remember, the two of us
年を重ねてた
piled up the years together.
また止まった 落とす針を良く流した
The dropped needle that stopped again, we let it flow so much
聞き飽きるほど変わらないね
until we were tired of listening—it hasn't changed.
変わらないで いられたのは君だけが
The only one who could stay the same was you.
無駄話ではぐらかして
Deflecting with idle chatter,
触れた先をためらうように
as if hesitating at the touch.
足踏みして ズれた針を余所に
Treading in place, aside from the misaligned clock hands,
歌い始めた息が
our breathing began to sync.
どうでもいいような夜だけど
It's an ordinary, don't-care kind of night, but
響めき 煌めきと君も 踊ろう
let's dance with the hustle, the sparkle, and you.
どうでもいいような夜だけど 二人刻もう
It's an ordinary night, let's mark the time together.
透き通った白い肌も その笑った無邪気な顔も
Your translucent white skin, your smiling innocent face—
変わらないね 変わらないで いられるのは今だけか
nothing has changed, can we stay like this only now?
見つめるほどに 溢れるメモリー
The more I gaze, the more memories overflow.
浮つく心にコーヒーを
Pouring coffee for a fluttering heart,
乱れた部屋に散らばったメロディー 混ざり合ってよう
a scattered melody in a disordered room, let's blend together.
もう一度
Once more.
どうでもいいような夜だけど
It's an ordinary, don't-care kind of night, but
響めき 煌めきと君も 踊ろう
let's dance with the hustle, the sparkle, and you.
夜は長い おぼつかない 今にも止まりそうなミュージック
The night is long and uncertain, the music feels like it could stop anytime.
君といたい 溺れてたい 明日がこなくたって もういいの
I want to be with you, to drown in you, even if tomorrow never comes, it's fine.
どうでもいいような夜だけど
It's an ordinary, don't-care kind of night, but
響めき 煌めきと君も 踊ろう
let's dance with the hustle, the sparkle, and you.
どうでもいいから僕だけを
So whoever cares, look only at me.
ふらつき よろめきながらも 踊ろう
Staggering and stumbling along, let's dance.
どうでもいいような夜だけど 二人刻もう
It's an ordinary night, let's mark the time together.
透き通った白い肌も その笑った無邪気な顔も
Your translucent white skin, your smiling innocent face—
変わらないね 変わらないで いられるのは今だけか
nothing has changed, can we stay like this only now?
見つめるほどに 溢れるメモリー
The more I gaze, the more memories overflow.
浮つく心にコーヒーを
Pouring coffee for a fluttering heart,
乱れた部屋に散らばったメロディー 混ざり合ってよう
a scattered melody in a disordered room, let's blend together.
もう一度
Once more.
どうでもいいような夜だけど
It's an ordinary, don't-care kind of night, but
響めき 煌めきと君も 踊ろう
let's dance with the hustle, the sparkle, and you.
夜は長い おぼつかない 今にも止まりそうなミュージック
The night is long and uncertain, the music feels like it could stop anytime.
君といたい 溺れてたい 明日がこなくたって もういいの
I want to be with you, to drown in you, even if tomorrow never comes, it's fine.
どうでもいいような夜だけど
It's an ordinary, don't-care kind of night, but
響めき 煌めきと君も 踊ろう
let's dance with the hustle, the sparkle, and you.
どうでもいいから僕だけを
So whoever cares, look only at me.
ふらつき よろめきながらも 踊ろう
Staggering and stumbling along, let's dance.
どうでもいいような夜だけど 二人刻もう
It's an ordinary night, let's mark the time together.
二人刻もう
Let's carve out our time together.
Yay! I hope you enjoyed those two songs!
Tadi kita dengerin dua lagu lagi ya!
We just listened to two more songs!
Wow, untuk yang pertama, tamu untuk lagu ini, lagu apa tuh? Idol, adalah Kobo!
Wow, for our first guest for this song... what song was it? Idol, it's Kobo!
Jadi kenapa sih pengen nyanyi sama Kobo? Why do I want to sing with Kobo ya? Soalnya tuh kebetulan anak kecil ini didrop gitu di depan rumah tante, jadi tante mengajak dianya lagi babysitting sambil diajak nyanyi-nyanyi aja, gitu.
So why did I want to sing with Kobo? Why do you want to sing with Kobo, you ask? Well, as it happens, this little kid was dropped off in front of auntie's house, so auntie invited her while babysitting and just sang along with her, you know.
I wanted to sing with her because I don't know, I just felt like... I felt, yeah... um she was dropped off in front of my door, so I thought it would be nice to, you know, babysit while singing with her, I guess.
And yeah! I thought the song fits both our voice very well and we're both blue, you know, it's kind of like the tall blue and the tiny blue, so it all it all makes sense. It's nice, right? I hope you guys enjoyed our performance.
And yeah! I thought the song fits both our voices very well and we're both blue, you know, it's kind of like the tall blue and the tiny blue, so it all makes sense. It's nice, right? I hope you guys enjoyed our performance.
Yeah! And for Night dancer, our guest is... Katanya opii? It's Calli!
Yeah! And for Night Dancer, our guest is... They said Opi? It's Calli!
Calli is someone I've always admired. She has such a cool voice, such strong, elegant, I don't know how to say it, but just, you know, very cool, very cool person, very cool vocals. And this time I want to sing something more chill and elegant, not elegant, chill, chill with her.
Calli is someone I've always admired. She has such a cool voice, such strong, elegant—I don't know how to say it, but just, you know, very cool, very cool person, very cool vocals. And this time I want to sing something more chill and elegant—not elegant, chill, chill with her.
How was our how was our dance?
How was our—how was our dance?
I think, uh, both of us has, you know, different individual styles and it's really interesting to see them together in a performance.
I think both of us have, you know, different individual styles and it's really interesting to see them together in a performance.
And then next up is... Did anybody guess it? It's a DJ segment! Sigiwa nanto...
And then next up is... Did anybody guess it? It's a DJ segment! Next up is...
DJ part desu! I'm going to be changing outfits, cuz I think, I don't know, maybe if we're going to DJ, maybe we we need something more, you know, more fit for DJing kan bajunya ya? Oke, so I'm going to get changed, okay? See you soon!
It's the DJ part! I'm going to be changing outfits, cuz I think, I don't know, maybe if we're going to DJ, maybe we need something more, you know, more fit for DJing, right? Okay, so I'm going to get changed, okay? See you soon!
星が揺らいで 夢を見ている
Stars are swaying, dreaming a dream.
焦がれたその音が待ってるの
That yearning sound is waiting for me.
きらめくカラー 秘めてる日々に
In days hiding sparkling colors,
伝えるこのメロディ
I'll convey this melody.
窓から覗いた 雨の降る街並みを
Peeking out the window at the rainy townscape,
弾ける音だから ポケットに詰め込んで Let's dance now
it's a popping sound, so I'll pack it in my pocket and let's dance now.
君の好きな (ちょっとcoolでpopな party song)
Your favorite (a little cool and pop party song)
キラーチューンのステップに乗せて
Ride the killer tune's step.
魔法のような (もっとvivid passion shiny ray)
Like magic (more vivid passion shiny ray)
ライトが私を照らしている
Lights are illuminating me.
星を紡いで 夢を描くよ
Spinning stars, painting a dream.
焦がれたその声が呼んでいるの
That yearning voice is calling out.
きらめくカラー まとった君に 届けるこのメロディ
To you, draped in sparkling colors, I deliver this melody.
このままでじちゃ終わらない (終わらない)
It won't end just like this (won't end)
Specialな stage 踊り明かすの (明かすそう)
Dancing the night away on a special stage (let's dance it away)
このままでじっとしていられない (そうさせない)
I can't just stand still like this (won't let you)
走り出そうよ 明日は晴れるから
Let's start running, because tomorrow will be clear.
星を紡いで 夢を描くよ
Spinning stars, painting a dream.
焦がれたその声が呼んでいるの
That yearning voice is calling out.
きらめくカラー まとった君に 届けるこのメロディ
To you, draped in sparkling colors, I deliver this melody.
このままでじちゃ終わらない (終わらない)
It won't end just like this (won't end)
Specialな stage 踊り明かすの (明かすそう)
Dancing the night away on a special stage (let's dance it away)
このままでじっとしていられない (そうさせない)
I can't just stand still like this (won't let you)
走り出そうよ 世界は変わるから
Let's start running, because the world will change.
退屈な日常 このままでいいの? 通知待って携帯見てばかりで
Is this boring everyday life fine as is? Just waiting for notifications and staring at my phone,
ハート止まっていても 心奮わせたいのだから これが show time 歩みだしていこうか
even if my heart stopped, I want to make my soul tremble, so this is show time, shall we start walking?
1, 2, 3で 星を見つけて
Find a star with 1, 2, 3,
4, 5, 6で 君を見つけたの
Found you with 4, 5, 6,
7, 8, 9で 夢を見つめて
Gaze at a dream with 7, 8, 9...
退屈な日常 このままでいいのか?
Is this boring everyday life okay as it is?
通知待ってケータイ見てばかりで
Just waiting for notifications and looking at my phone
ハート止まってても 心 奮わせたいの
Even if my heart stopped, I want to make it race
これからがshow time 步きだしていこうか
From here on is show time, let's start walking
1, 2, 3で 星を見つけて
Find a star with 1, 2, 3
4, 5, 6で 君を見つけたの
Found you with 4, 5, 6
7, 8, 9で 夢を見つめて
Stare at a dream with 7, 8, 9
9・0・2で 瞳が開くの
My eyes open at 9, 0, 2
ツギハギ カラダに溢れていくよ memory
Memory overflowing in this patchwork body
ズキズキ アタマに特効薬の 我爱你
Wo Ai Ni, the cure for a throbbing head
つぎつぎ 脳内に happillie な melody
Happillie melody in my brain one after another
うきうき な パーティー are you ready ? ya
Excited party, are you ready? Ya!
jollie jollie night ★ ドレスコード なんて ない の
Jolly jolly night ★ There's no dress code
shiny time is now 閃いてく よ 舞台
Shiny time is now, the stage sparkles
crazy kureiji dance 心 踊る よう な ジャーニー
Crazy kureiji dance, a heart-dancing journey
見つけた ん だ とっておき の 居場所
I found a special place
bad l lie な こと も たまに あんご
Sometimes there are bad lies too
sad l lie な 雨 が 降る こと も あんご
Sometimes sad rain falls too
だけど it 's all right ! いじける 暇 no time !
But it's all right! No time to sulk!
これから が show time 虹 が かかる よ !
From here on is show time, a rainbow appears!
動悸 が する くらい 今 が 好き な の
I love the present so much my heart races
時 忘れる くらい 熱狂 し て 万々歳
Enthusiastic enough to forget time, marvelous!
体温 上がっ て る トゥナイト bpm は 上限 無い
Body temperature rising tonight, no limit to BPM
際 限 ない この 鬼才 誰 に 共有 し たい !
Who do I want to share this endless genius with!
アストロノーツ 満天 の スター リー ナイト
Astronauts, a starry night filling the sky
泣く 子 黙る 三千 世界
The three thousand worlds where crying children fall silent
主役 アタシ 以外 に 無い じゃん ?
Isn't the protagonist anyone other than me?
put your hands up ミュータント 集会
Put your hands up, mutant gathering
ミラーボール 反射 する ブルーライト
Mirror ball reflecting blue light
アンサンブル で デンジャー じゃ ない ?
Isn't it dangerous with an ensemble?
i'll never break down.
everlasting knife.
例えば 君 が 私 の 意志 を 制御 しよう とも
Even if you try to control my will,
無味乾燥に 望み澄ました否定を投げる
Indifferently casting a cleared denial
時代 の 最中 に 過去 の 遺物 が
In the midst of the times, relics of the past
寄る 辺 なく 生まれ
are born without a shelter,
異質な孤独に 芽生えられても
even if nurtured by alien solitude.
擦り切れる まで
Until worn out,
零れ た 温度 に 浸さ れ て
soaked in the spilled temperature,
折り紙付き の 心 が 咲く
a guaranteed heart blooms.
張り詰めた 収まらない 声 を 聞け
Listen to the strained, irrepressible voice,
私 が 真 の 刃 と
as I become the true blade,
ただ 刻ん で 裂い て 切っ て
just carving, tearing, cutting,
唱え た 道 を 示す
and showing the path chanted.
指図 も なく 愛情 も なく
Without instructions, without affection,
i'll never break down.
everlasting knife.
例えば 君 が 私 の 意味 を 問いかける の なら
If you question my meaning,
極不自然に 乾燥し尽くした境地を見せる
showing an extremely unnatural, parched state.
神秘 の 情火 は 夜 の 帳 を
The mystical passion without lowering the night's curtain
下ろさ ず に 叫ぶ
cries out,
理想 の 起源 が 波 を 立て て も
even if the origin of ideals makes waves,
貫く だけ と
just piercing through.
今 私 は 鉄 の 覚悟 を
Now I forge, burn, strike
ただ 鍛え て 焼い て 打っ て
the iron resolution
無謀 な 弱 さ を 消す
to erase reckless weakness.
微塵 も なく 揺るぎ も なく
Without a speck, without a shake,
kiss me ! keep those lips from wandering off
Kiss me! Keep those lips from wandering off
tell me every sweet and tender thought !
Tell me every sweet and tender thought!
give me all you have to give and more . . .
Give me all you have to give and more...
fantasy 's where futures are born !
Fantasy's where futures are born!
can you feel the beat ? the rhythm , the tune . . .
Can you feel the beat? The rhythm, the tune...
your heart and mine - the countdown . . .
Your heart and mine - the countdown...
if you feel something coming to you ,
If you feel something coming to you,
believe it and scream it aloud !
Believe it and scream it aloud!
i don't think “ i ' ll miss you . . . ” anymore , like i did the day you left .
I don't think "I'll miss you..." anymore, like I did the day you left.
there 's so many just like you , i could use instead ！
There's so many just like you, I could use instead!
‘ cause passion burning bright only hurts you in the end .
'Cause passion burning bright only hurts you in the end.
this city will swallow the pain . . .
This city will swallow the pain...
tomorrow 's another today . . .
Tomorrow's another today...
curtain call 's at dawn , darling ！ showtime ！
Curtain call's at dawn, darling! Showtime!
spend our moment dancing in the moonlight ！
Spend our moment dancing in the moonlight!
‘ til your gaze starts swaying with my body . . .
'Til your gaze starts swaying with my body...
keep your eyes on me ！
Keep your eyes on me!
take me somewhere , deep into the night . . .
Take me somewhere, deep into the night...
touch me - here , there , anywhere you like ！
Touch me - here, there, anywhere you like!
trust me ！ won't you let me look inside ？
Trust me! Won't you let me look inside?
fantasies and futures collide …
Fantasies and futures collide...
it 's just the two of us beneath the starry sky . . .
It's just the two of us beneath the starry sky...
if the only way to keep on living is “ keep on living strong ！ ”
If the only way to keep on living is "Keep on living strong!"
then , you can keep the kindness , ‘ cause i 'm moving on ！
Then, you can keep the kindness, 'cause I'm moving on!
ド・キ・ド・キ ・ し て rouge ?
Do-ki-do-ki-shite rouge?
いき ます よ ～ ！
Here we go~!
無罪 ！ 無罪 ！ 美少女無罪 ！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girl innocent!
マリン ！ マリン ！ マリン は 無罪 ！
Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!
やっぱり キラキラ もっと クラクラ
Still sparkling, even more dizzy
ねぇ 、 言った よ ね ？
Hey, you said it right?
年齢 なんて 関係 ないっ て さ
That age doesn't matter
そういう めんどくさい の も
Even such troublesome things
含め て 愛し て くれるっ て
You'd love including that
ねぇねぇ 、 言った よ ね ？ 言って ない ？
Hey hey, you said it right? Or didn't you?
ふーん 、 そういう こと いう ん だ
Hmm, is that what you say?
ちなみに この 船 で は
By the way, on this ship,
美少女無罪 が 適用 さ れ ます けど ？
beautiful girl innocence applies, you know?
まかせ て ！ 魔法 で 若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenated by magic
ヒミツ の 素顔 は キミ に だけ
My secret bare face is just for you
トクベツ です よ ～ ？
Is it special~?
あぁ … アタシ 厄介 よ
Ah... I'm troublesome
あぁ … 港 なんか じゃ
Ah... at ports or places like that
はしゃげ ない わ 近頃 は ね
I can't get excited lately
宝 の 島 に し て ほしい 気分
I feel like turning it into Treasure Island
出航 ー ！ ！
Set sail!!
キュート は 正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, beautiful girl innocence
キミ の 一番 目指し て ヨーソロー ！
Aiming to be your number one, yosoro!
本当 は 自信 ない けど 頑張っ ちゃう ん
I'm actually not confident, but I'll do my best
ahoy ！ ！
Ahoy!!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん
Kyu kyu kyurun
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurunrun
恋 する 気持ち 17 歳
Feelings of love at 17 years old
0 時 に なっ ちゃう ワ オトナ の 時間
It becomes 0 o'clock, adult time
やっぱり キラキラ もっと クラクラ
Still sparkling, even more dizzy
ド・キ・ド・キ ・ し て rouge ?
Do-ki-do-ki-shite rouge?
まだ 早い ♡
Still too early ♡
だっ だっ ダメ です か ？
Is-is-is it no good?
フリル の 服装 着 たら
If I wear frilly clothes
そんな こと 、 ない よ
There's no such thing,
だっっだっ て ば
I'm telling you!
魔法少女 に なって みたい
I want to become a magical girl
ギリギリ 有罪 ! ?
Barely guilty!?
進路 は なん なん 星
Course is Nannan star
ちょっぴり 足 ん ない 積極 性 ？
A little lacking in positivity?
結局 キミ も もっと 若い 子 ？
In the end, you want a younger girl too?
なんて関係ないってさ そういうめんどくさいのも含めて愛してくれないって
"You said it doesn't matter, and won't love me including all that troublesome stuff."
ねえねえ 言ってよ 言ってない
"Hey, hey, say it." — "I didn't say it."
ふーん、そういうこと言うんだ。ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？
"Hmph, is that what you'd say? By the way, 'cute girl immunity' applies on this ship!"
任せて！ 魔法で笑わせに
"Leave it to me! I'll make you smile with magic!"
行くぞ 船上は君だけ特別だしよ
"Let's go! On deck, you're the only special one."
あーしや街よ 港となんかじゃ
"This town, compared to a port,"
はしゃげないわ、ちかごろまでは
"I can't get excited, at least until recently."
宝島の島民にしてほしい気分じゃん？
"Don't you feel like making me a resident of Treasure Island?"
キュッ、キュッ、キュルン、キュッ、キュルン 君の息が根を出してやっと
"Kyu, kyu, kyurun, kyu, kyurun, finally catching your breath at last."
本当は心配ないけど頑張っちゃう
"Though I'm really not worried, I'll do my best!"
キュッ、キュッ、キュルン、キュッ、キュルン 恋する気持ち中7日
"Kyu, kyu, kyurun, kyu, kyurun, 7 days in the middle of love."
てっぺんになっちゃおは 大人のお時間
"Let's reach the top, it's grownups' time."
ドキドキして ぬし！ まだ早い
"My heart is pounding! Master! It's still too early."
恋する気持ち中7日 てっぺんになっちゃおは 大人のお時間
"7 days in the middle of love, let's reach the top, it's grownups' time."
ドキドキして ぬし！ まだ早い
"My heart is pounding! Master! It's still too early."
まわれまれこそがQueen お仕置きしてあげるわ
"Spin around, for you are the Queen, I'll punish you."
逆らうなら痛い痛いお灸を据えてあげましょう
"If you rebel, I'll give you painful moxibustion."
So what the heck? The fishy with its golden eye, still got your tongue-tied?
まわれまれこそがQueen お仕置きしてあげるわ
"Spin around, for you are the Queen, I'll punish you."
逆らうなら痛い痛いお灸を据えてあげましょう
"If you rebel, I'll give you painful moxibustion."
So what the heck? The fishy with its golden eye, still got your tongue-tied?
It's been a long right way, we're reclaiming the queen of the night
バカなママでもオッケー これだってとっておきでスペシャル
"Even if you're a foolish mama, it's okay, this is a special treat."
あらあらナイトジャッフェ 可愛くって被ってストロングから
"My, my, night jaffe, cute and covered, starting strong."
ずっと君の隣じっと見てる分かり合い愛 愛
"Staring right beside you forever, mutual love, love, love."
やまない雨 世界に二人きりえいっ
"An endless rain, just the two of us in this world, eit!"
傷むように心 今この頃にどんな痛みさえも愛の形
"So my heart aches, right now, even any pain is the shape of love."
運命に結ばれた指を握る約束をしよう
"Let's make a promise to clasp our fingers bound by fate."
Love me, love me
私がいらない 私がいらない 私がいらない 私がいらない
"I'm not needed, I'm not needed, I'm not needed, I'm not needed."
Love me, love me... 君がいらない 君がいらない 君がいらない
"Love me, love me... You're not needed, you're not needed, you're not needed."
Sing Love Me
everything was easy i did it all alone so effortlessly
i spread my wings and let my magic unfold got all problems solved
without any setbacks there is nothing uncontrolled
but there's no way i can begin dream life that i need to win
"But there's no way I can begin the dream life that I need to win."
i need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
i know i gotta soar a little higher hope all turns to be the things i desire
layaknya burung merak yang bersayap kan kutaklukan gelap
"Like a winged peacock, I will conquer the darkness."
dengan sihir angin kan ku ajak semua yg terlelap 'tuk bangkit melawan dunia
"With wind magic, I'll invite everyone asleep to rise and fight the world."
we'll never give up as long as we got the strength in ourselves we could rise above the pain
we're stronger than them walking step by step trusting my own pace giving me what i deserve to have
let's go just believe me let it go they'll never bring me down just believe me let it go
it'll never bring us down just believe me won't let their cruelty stealin' my royalty and when the universe works against me i will just
"It'll never bring us down, just believe me, won't let their cruelty steal my royalty, and when the universe works against me, I will just..."
let it go
if it's spicy, just sip some tea
sip some tea
let it go
if it's spicy, just sip some tea, let it go
if it's spicy
just sip some tea
let it go
if it's spicy, just sip some tea
just sip some tea
let it go
i've been livin' carefree
there's no bitter words in the world that could affect me
i spread my wings and let my magic unfold
not letting it show
stings but i'm bigger than my feelings so that'll be enough
there is no way i can begin
dream life that i need to win
i need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
i know i gotta be better than ever
hope all turns to be sweeter than ever
layaknya burung merak yang bersayap kan kutaklukkan gelap
Like a winged peacock, I will conquer the darkness
dengan sihir angin kan kuajak semua yg terlelap 'tuk bangkit melawan dunia
with wind magic, I'll invite everyone asleep to rise up against the world!
we'll never give up! as long as we got
the strength in ourselves
we could rise above the pain
we're stronger than them
walking step by step, trusting my own pace
giving me what i deserve to have
let's go
they'll never bring me down
it'll never bring us down
won't let their cruelty steal in my royalty
and when the universe works against me i will just
let it go
if it's spicy, just sip some tea
let it go, if it's spicy, just sip some tea
let it go
Attention please!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Or are you by any chance a MERAKyats who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
My name is Pavolia Reine, and I'm going to be here explaining briefly what is going on with Pavolia Reine's membership.
(That is mine, by the way.)
At The Royaltea, our super advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights, which you can constantly show off every time you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties, which also means membership-exclusive streams
in which we can have various talks, play games together, and do other miscellaneous member involvements.
Like what, you might ask? Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed, but it is a paramount development training in which we aim to build a community of people who like living dangerously.
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
いいね快晴じゃん
The weather's perfect, not a cloud in the sky,
雲一つないよ
not a single cloud in sight.
真っ赤な太陽
A bright red sun,
君を知りたいよ
I want to get to know you.
あとはオレ等次第
The rest is up to us,
今日は抱きしめたい
I want to hold you today.
波打ち際の熱い決意
A passionate resolve by the water's edge,
甲子園球児さながらの闘志
fighting spirit just like Koshien ballplayers.
でも打率は9厘
But my batting average is .009,
オレのジャンルにSORRY
sorry to my genre.
まさに語り継がれるストーリー
Truly a story passed down through generations,
1人で遊ぶのは今夜で終わり?
is playing alone ending tonight?
上海ハニーと
With Shanghai Honey
浜辺社交ダンス
and beach social dancing,
見つめっぱなし
staring unblinkingly
たまんねぇ女神
at a stunning goddess!
上海ハニーと
With Shanghai Honey
エイジアン・ランデヴー
and an Asian rendezvous,
寄せては返す下心とモラル
ebb and flow of ulterior motives and morals.
僕君のことよく知らないけれど何かトキメイてます
I don't know you well, but my heart is fluttering!
Yo巧みな話術
Yo, clever conversational skill
彼女を翻弄
to toy with her,
母性本能くすぐるトーク
talk that tickles maternal instincts.
これがオレの理想像
This is my ideal image,
でも理想は理想
but an ideal is an ideal,
また「優しそう」で終わりそう
and it'll probably end with "you seem nice".
いやいや今夜こそはGET
No no, tonight's the night I get her,
セイシをかけたまさに決闘
a duel where we stake our youth!
今が旬 oretachiの青春
Our youth is in full bloom right now,
「しまっていこう!!」気合十分
"Let's keep it tight!!" full of fighting spirit.
上海ハニーと浜辺社交ダンス
With Shanghai Honey and beach social dancing,
見つめっぱなし たまんねぇ女神
staring unblinkingly at a stunning goddess!
上海ハニーと エイジアン・ランデヴー
With Shanghai Honey and an Asian rendezvous,
寄せては返す下心とモラル
ebb and flow of ulterior motives and morals.
何か純愛じゃない? なんてね
This might just be an innocent love,
そっか そりゃ無理だよな。だってそう僕君のことよく知らないけれど
nah, that's impossible 'cause I don't even know you,
何かトキメイてます
but I think I'm in love!
そっか そりゃ無理だよな
I see, I guess that's impossible.
だってそう 僕
'Cause you see, I...
君のことよく知らないけれど
I don't even know you that well, but
何かトキメイてます
My heart is fluttering.
Se... sendok, Tante...
S... spoon, Auntie...
Sendok, Tante...
Spoon, Auntie...
Ampun! Ampun, Tante!
Mercy! Mercy, Auntie!
上海ハニーと 浜辺社交ダンス
A social dance on the beach with a Shanghai Honey
見つめっぱなし たまんねぇ女神
Can't stop staring at that gorgeous goddess
上海ハニーと エイジアン・ランデヴー
An Asian rendezvous with a Shanghai Honey
寄せては返す 下心とモラル
My heart swings between ulterior motives and morals
何か純愛じゃないかもね
Maybe this isn't just pure love.
そっか そりゃそうだよな
I see, I guess that's how it is.
だってそう
'Cause you see,
僕 君のことよく知らないけれど
I don't even know you that well, but
何かトキメイてます
My heart is fluttering.
ホラロ！
Holoro!
Ollie!
Kobo!
Reine!
Zeta!
Who--!
Happy Birthday Reine!
やるとは思わなかった！
Yeah! I didn't think we'd actually do it!
How was it? いかがだったでしょうか？
How was it? How did you like it?
That was performance after performance!
First up, we have the DJ performance! Wow.
For those of you guys who don't know yet, well, previously I've done a little bit of a 45-minute DJ performance on my channel.
If you guys haven't checked it out, please do check it out. But you know, some people have been asking, when is DJ Reine coming back?
So you know what? I thought this would be the perfect opportunity to include it, well, even though we were on a bit of a time constraint.
So I had to do something super short, you know, believe me, it's part of... um, you know, I really, really wanted to include a lot more songs. It's actually, you know, just a lot of Hololive songs I really, really liked.
I think the songs are like super, super danceable. And did you notice, you know, we had like Hololive songs back-to-back? I really, I really, really wanted to make it work.
And yeah, it did work. You know, so yeah, maybe next time I will do a longer one, you know, so I can like, just a lot more songs. I thought it's just like fun, you know, I want to share, share and play all the Hololive songs that I like.
And maybe in the future I can do more. And also, you heard my song, Ship Shanti!
But it's a little bit different, right? The person who did this beautiful remix, thank you so much RedShift-san!
今回のリミックスをいただいた方は、RedShiftさんです。They made it sound really, really cool!
The person who provided this remix is RedShift-san. They made it sound really, really cool!
Yes! I really, really, really like it. I hope you guys liked it too. And then, my gen-mates came with me and we sang and performed Shanghai Honey together.
I've always wanted to do a super, super, super fun song with Holoro because you know, it's just a vibe. It's just a vibe, you know? We're all like super like, woo, yes!
So I thought Shanghai Honey was the perfect fit for the three of us. Yeah, it was really cool, right? And look at these sunglasses, very nice, right?
Well, today's birthday live concert is about to reach the final song.
But before that, I have two announcements to make! The first announcement is...
Birthday celebration merch! Tada!
There's limited supplies, so get yours ASAP! And here it is! The merch key visuals are illustrated by Iida Pochi-mama. Yay, so cute right?
And we can take a look at the items one by one. Yukata... Yukata barangnya satu-satu. Jeng-jeng! Ada apa aja nih?
And we can take a look at the items one by one. Let's check the items one by one. Ta-da! What do we have here?
Oh my god! Ada apa itu? Oh my god!
Oh my god! What is that? Oh my god!
Yang pertama adalah ini! Ada kaos...
The first one is this! There's a t-shirt...
Tapi ada oversized T-shirt, loose-fit T-shirt,
There's an oversized T-shirt, a loose-fit T-shirt,
terbangnya sang putri neon. Anjay, keren banget enggak sih?
Flight of the Neon Princess. Damn, isn't that cool?
This is a big silhouette t-shirt that can be worn by everybody.
Kita bisa lihat enggak sih, can we see? Can we see the zoom out version of the shirt? Oh, enggak ada yang ini, udah. Ya udah.
Can we see? Can we see the zoom-out version of the shirt? Oh, there's no other. Oh well.
And please don't forget to wear it to events, okay?
Pokoknya keren banget. Nanti kalau misalnya, "kamu fansnya siapa ya?" Terus kayak, "jreng! Aku adalah fansnya Reine," gitu. You can show your oshi through your shirt. Ya pokoknya keren sih, menurut aku, ya.
Anyway, it's super cool. Later when someone asks, "Whose fan are you?" you can go, "Ta-da! I'm Reine's fan!" You can show your oshi through your shirt. It's just really cool, I think.
And then the next one, ada ini!
And then the next one, we have this!
Eoh, ada apa tu? Ada tote bag! It's a reversible tote bag pakai zipper. Menurut aku keren banget sih. It fits A4 size and is designed with a zipper for easy use.
Ooh, what's this? A tote bag! It's a reversible tote bag with a zipper. I think it's really cool. It fits A4 size and is designed with a zipper for easy use.
Jadi kalau misalnya kalian lagi ya nonton konser, lagi hype-hype, terus kayak kalian enggak perlu takut barangkali kalian tumpah semua, gitu. Kalau menurut aku sih keren banget.
So if you're watching a concert and getting super hyped, you don't have to worry about your things spilling everywhere. I think it's really cool.
You don't need to be afraid when you're like super hype and finally your things fall all over the place because, jump all over the place because you're too hype. Yeah, so I think it's very, very perfect with the zipper, of course, gitu.
You don't need to be afraid when you're super hyped and your stuff is flying everywhere because you're jumping around. Yeah, so I think it's very, very perfect with the zipper, of course.
And you can also attach keychains in the tote bag so you can show off. And what if you don't have any keychains? What do you do?
And you can also attach keychains to the tote bag so you can show off. What if you don't have any keychains? What do you do?
Next one, we have this, this, this, this! Hadeuh, shopping sendiri aku. Heboh sendiri.
Next one, we have this, this, this, this! Oh man, I'm shopping by myself and getting so excited.
We have Mark of the Peafowl Keychain. Seru banget, cute keychain featuring aurora fabric and metal charm.
We have the Mark of the Peafowl Keychain. A super cute keychain featuring aurora fabric and a metal charm.
Ini bagus banget karena ada kain hologram dan logamnya, gitu ya. Jadi kalau misalnya kalian enggak punya atau punya pun enggak apa-apa, pokoknya harus gantungin ini biar pas.
This is great because it has holographic fabric and metal, so whether you have one or not, you should hang this to match.
You can hang it like schwing! gitu and show off your tote bag and show off your keychain with the shirt, gitu kalau menurut aku sih perfect banget.
You can hang it like *schwing!* and show off your tote bag and your keychain with the shirt. I think it's just perfect.
And then, that's not all! There is one more thing!
This is the next one. A birthday situational voice! Yay!
Seru banget enggak sih? Pokoknya isinya apa? Apa ya? Rahasia deh. Pokoknya it's a secret. You have to listen to know what it's about, but it will have something to do with this whole performance.
Isn't it exciting? What's in it? What could it be? It's a secret! You have to listen to know what it's about, but it will have something to do with this whole performance.
Pokoknya keren aja sih. Menurut aku, ya gitu, pokoknya keren deh pokoknya. I will zoot, pokoknya you have to listen. You have to listen to find out and tell me what you guys think, okay?
Anyway, it's just really cool. You have to listen to find out and tell me what you guys think, okay?
And by the way, this voice pack will be sold separately, not as part of the merchandise set, so please do keep that in mind, okay?
And by the way, this voice pack will be sold separately, not as part of the merch set, so please do keep that in mind, okay?
And also, here's a special bonus you get for buying the good set.
And also, here's a special bonus you get for buying the full set.
Bonus spesial ya buat yang beli yang komplit. Ada hand-signed polaroid, cheki-style bromide cards, bromide bergaya Polaroid bertandatangan.
A special bonus for those who buy the complete set. There's a hand-signed Polaroid-style cheki bromide card.
Pokoknya everybody will get the card, but there's a limited quantity. So, ya pokoknya cepetan-cepetan aja, guys.
Everyone will get the card, but there's a limited quantity, so you guys better hurry up.
And if you buy the full set, you will receive a card that can be used in the whole life official card game as a special bonus.
And if you buy the full set, you will receive a card that can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game as a special bonus.
Pokoknya bisa deh. Tapi apa namanya? Cuma dari ini ya, Hololive Official Store, gitu shop. Jadi it's a key hololive member card to show off your favorite, namanya oshi holomem card.
Yeah, you can. But it's only available from the Hololive Official Store/shop. It's a special Hololive member card to show off your favorite oshi.
Dan cuma ada di Jepang, bahasa Jepang, oke? Jadi, tapi bisanya belinya dari Official Store aja ya, guys.
And it's only in Japan, in Japanese, okay? But you can only buy it from the official store, guys.
So keep that in mind, hololive official shop only, gitu. And then, second announcement!
So keep that in mind, Hololive Official Shop only. And then, second announcement!
Kita ngebut banget nih, guys, pengumumannya. Ayo, ayo, second announcement, sekarang, sekarang, sekarang!
We're rushing through this announcement, guys! Come on, second announcement right now!
Second announcement, second announcement! Aku punya lagu baru! Aku punya lagu baru! Pokoknya kalian harus mendengarkan. Judulnya adalah "YUMMY YUMMY YUMMY", gitu.
Second announcement! I have a new song! I have a new song! You all have to listen to it. It's titled "YUMMY YUMMY YUMMY".
Jadi lyrics and composition-nya done by Hylensun. Pokoknya menurut aku sih keren banget ya, dan kayaknya tuh feels-nya it's crafted with a dark yet pop feel, gitu.
The lyrics and composition are done by Hylensun. I think it's really cool, and it feels like it's crafted with a dark yet pop feel.
Jadi kalau menurut aku sih, it's like mature, but also pop, gitu. Jadi it's a nice mix of both world. It will be released on September 10, 0000. So please be sure to listen to it.
So I think it's mature, but also pop. A nice mix of both worlds. It will be released on September 10th at 00:00, so please be sure to listen to it.
There might be time zone difference and stuff like that, but yeah, please do keep your eyes peeled, okay? And of course, this time we will be ending the live concert with this song, okay?
There might be time zone differences and stuff, but please keep your eyes peeled. And of course, we will be ending the live concert with this song, okay?
So, guys, please enjoy, okay? Yummy, yamu, yummy, kiite kudasai!
So guys, please enjoy, okay? Yummy, yamu, yummy, please listen to it!
Yummy, yummy, do do do...
Yummy, yummy, do-do-do...
Yami yamu, yami yamu, yami yamu, All Night Show!
Samidare no rainy...
Yami yami yami... bam, bam, bam, party!
Gokigen na ladies!
Yummy? ヤミ ドゥッ ドゥ、 yummy 病み do
Yummy? Yami dug-dug, yummy, yami, do
Yummy? ヤミ ドゥッ ドゥ
闇止む 悩みやヤミ all night show
Darkness stops, worries end, yami all night show
(bam+bam party!)
(月初のランウェイ)
(First month's runway)
(逃げ切りワンダー)
(Escaping wonderland)
放心調子？ なんだって 徘徊 曖昧 シャットダウン
Carefree mood? What's that? Wandering, vague shutdown
急成長 正常 難題は movin’ to 選択肢
Rapid growth, normal, trouble is movin' to choices
(引っ込みダウンイン さぁ？)
(Pulling downswing, huh?)
(ラッタッタ won’t you steal my heart?)
(Rat-tat-tat, won't you steal my heart?)
衝動 現実からの escape のりくるり s+o+s なら 燃え上がるわ 全身
Impulse, escape from reality, swaying, s.o.s., then blazing up whole-heartedly
(よくばりピーポー)
(Greedy people)
(yummy, yummy ジャスティス)
(Yummy, yummy justice)
one chance 狙う jackpot, 願いまわす gabut
One chance, aiming for jackpot, I'm begging you gabut
のるかそるか k!ll か ill かの look back show!
Ride or die, k!ll or ill look back show!
観戦？ 完成？ 貸せ！ 貸せ！
Spectating? Completed? Lend it! Lend it!
(おすとか 分岐？)
(Osu and분기?)
ah ズッキン ズッキン パラッパ 冷めないうちに入
Ah, thumping, thumping, para-pa, before it cools down inside
ah ズッキン ズッキン パラッパ お味はいかが？
Ah, thumping, thumping, para-pa, how does it taste?
ah 足りない まだ足りないの
Ah, it's not enough, still not enough
ah lonely night まだ足りないの？
Ah, lonely night, still not enough?
最高 臨界点 更新中
Highest critical point being updated right now
思考のマリアージュ 駆け足ドメスティック
Marriage of thoughts, rushing domestic
(右か左か)
(Right or left)
(逃げるが先だ)
(Running away comes first)
(卵が先だ)
(The egg comes first)
(ピースは揃った！)
(The pieces are set!)
sir baby baby baby もう時間がないわ
Sir, baby, baby, baby, there's no time left
ラリ ル ララ ルーリ 捕まえて ルルーラ 壊れる前に
Rari-ru-ra-ru-ri, catch and ru-ru-ra, before it breaks
ah ドッキン ドッキンパラッパ ルージュを付けて
Ah, thumping, thumping, para-pa, putting on rouge
ah party time まだ足りないわ
Ah, party time, still not enough?
ah 範囲外 もう消えそうだ
Ah, out of bounds, about to vanish already
こっち向いてよ 哀・二重
Look this way, sorrow, double
Birds NIGHT OUT - Pavolia Reine Birthday 2024
Birds NIGHT OUT: Pavolia Reine Birthday 2024